MarcusMo

Contact

[Address and contact number redacted for online version]

me@marcusmo.co.uk www.marcusmo.co.uk

Programming

C, C++

OpenMP, MPI Nvidia CUDA

HTML5, CSS3 JavaScript, jQuery

Profile

Becoming a post-graduate allowed for further specialism in exciting areas such as high performance computing, data mining, and advanced numerical analysis; building upon the theoretical knowledge gained from studying Mathematics. Outside of academia, my passions involve experimenting with modern web technologies to develop performant and engaging experiences.

Education

2012–2013 MSc Scientific Computing

The University of Warwick

Parallelisation of Simultaneous Eigenvector Computations

Explored parallelisation techniques with respect to finding newforms via simultaneous Hecke eigenspaces; relating to the construction and tabulation of elliptic curves. A multi-threaded strategy was built, with Boost libraries, on top of an existing open-source C++ serial implementation: Eclib.

2009–2012 BSc Mathematics

The University of Warwick

First Class (Hons.)

2007–2009 **A-Level**

Alcester Grammar School, Sixth Form

A-Level: AAA; AS-Level: A

2002–2007 **GCSE**

St. Benedict's Catholic High School

AS-Level: A; GCSE: A*A*A*A*A*A*A*A; GNVQ: Distinction

Experience

2009-Present LaTeX Tutorials

latextutorials.co.uk

Designer, Developer, Chief Editor

Developed an interactive tutorial website, by compiling a database of common mathematical statements, for others to learn the typesetting language. Later collaborated with peers to provide online documentation on LaTeX, with a focus on simplicity and low-entry level experience.

The site is used as an interactive teaching aid during seminars provided by the Warwick Maths Society.

2011-Present Virtual Futures

virtualfutures.co.uk

Designer, Developer

Collaborated with organisers and artists to develop an online archive for past and future conferences; built with Wordpress.

2010–2012 **TEDxWarwick**

tedxwarwick.co.uk

Media Team Member, Design Consultant

Designed yearly event motifs, programmes and other advertising materials. Developed the TEDxWarwick 2011 website, and Facebook marketing pages for TEDxWarwick 2012.

2011–2012 Warwick Student Cinema

Chief Editor

Organised and coordinated volunteers for copy-writing and graphics sourcing; contributing to the termly film programme. Provided training and support for QuarkXPress.

Interests

professional: software development, high performance computing, parallel programming, web development and performance **personal:** badminton, mathematics, UX design, Go, typography.